# Kaloyan Penev

**Computer Vision Engineer** 



# **ABOUT ME**

Problem-solver interested in machine learning and computer graphics. Professional experience using Unity for NCCA Bournemouth University on the VISTA AR project. Familiar with Object Oriented and Entity-Component-System programming paradigms. Adaptive and creative in team environments.

# **PROJECTS**

#### HAND POSE RECOGNITION

Python / YOLOv4 / Darknet

Real time speed on consumer-grade GPUs using input from ordinary phone cameras. Built with the YOLOv4 FCNN.

#### **GAME ENGINE - eudaimonia**

C++17 / C / OpenGL / GLSL

Data-oriented ECS framework in native C++17 as backbone. 3D Physically Based Renderer made with OpenGL 3.3 as graphics system.

- **.** +44 7500 652536
- @ kdpenev@gmail.com
- https://penev.me

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### JUNIOR UNITY DEVELOPER

Bournemouth University • Feb 2020 - Jul 2020

- Development and profiling of AR apps in **Unity**
- Performance optimization for mobile devices
- Shader programming with HLSL and Shader Graph

#### STUDENT AMBASSADOR

Bournemouth University • Sep 2018 - Present

- Active engagement in the Admissions division
- Garnered rich teamwork experience
- Improved presenting and communication skills

# **EDUCATION**

#### **BSc GAMES SOFTWARE ENGINEERING**

Bournemouth University • Sept 2018 – Jun 2021 First class Honours (Predicted)

- Graphics and Computational Programming 83.03%
- Game Engine Programming 79.00%
- Al Game Programming 75.50%

## LANGUAGES









